And now we finally have the tools to write
ついに勾配降下アルゴリズムの疑似コードを
the pseudocode for the grading descent algorithm,
書くためのツールができ
and it goes like this.
このようになります
Step one, start with random weights w_one up to w_n and b which will give us a line,
ステップ1 ランダム重みw1からwnとbで始めます これが直線になり
and not just a line, but the whole probability function given by sigmoid of w x plus b.
ただの直線ではなく シグモイドwx+bによって与えられる全体確率関数です
Now for every point we'll calculate the error,
今度は すべてのポイントについてエラーを計算し
and as we can see the error is high for
誤って分類されたポイントについては
misclassified points and small for correctly classified points.
エラーが高く 正しく分類されたポイントは小くなっています
Now for every point with coordinates x_one up to x_n,
今度は座標x1からxnまでのすべてのポイントについて
we update w_i by adding the learning rate
学習率αにwiに関するエラー関数をかけたものを加えることによって
alpha times the partial derivative of the error function with respect to w_i.
wiを更新します
We also update b by adding alpha times
またαにbに関するエラー関数の偏微分を
the partial derivative of the error function with respect to be.
掛けたものを加えることによってにbを更新します
This gives us new weights,
これによって新しい重み
w_i_prime and then new bias b_prime.
wi素数と新しいバイアスb素数が得られます
Now we've already calculated these partial derivatives and we
これらの偏微分はすでに計算してあり
know that they are y_hat minus y times
wiに関する微分は
x_i for the derivative with respect to w_i
yハットマイナスyかけるxiであり
and y_hat minus y for the derivative with respect to b.
bに関する微分はyハットマイナスyです
So that's how we'll update the weights.
これが重みを更新する方法です
Now repeat this process until the error is small,
このプロセスをエラーが小さくなるまで繰り返すか
or we can repeat it a fixed number of times.
一定回数だけ繰り返します
The number of times is called the epochs and we'll learn them later.
回数はエポックと呼ばれ 後で学習します
Now this looks familiar,
これは見覚えがあります
have we seen something like that before?
以前に見たことがありませんか
Well, we look at the points and what each point is doing is
ポイントを見て 各ポイントが何をしているかを見ます
it's adding a multiple of itself into the weights of
自分自身の倍数を直線の重みに加えて
the line in order to get the line to move closer towards it if it's misclassified.
誤って分類されている場合に直線を近づけます
That's pretty much what the Perceptron algorithm is doing.
パーセプトロンアルゴリズムが何を行うか かなりよくわかります
So in the next video, we'll look at
次のビデオでは
the similarities because it's a bit suspicious how similar they are.
どの程度似ているか少し疑わしいので 類似性を見ます